Mae Craford

Summary

I am a creative spirit, enabling clients deepest dreams to turn tangible. My experiences with developing effective branding, UI/UX design, prototyping websites, and diverse clients will assure your safety in my capable hands. You can find a portfolio of my work at <a href="mailto:m

Education

Parsons School of Design

Communication Design • New York, New York

05/2021

- Graduated summa cum laude-3.7+ GPA
- Received a Deans Merit Scholarship 2017-2021

Skills

- HTML/CSS
- · Customer Service
- UI/UX design
- Color Theory

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Leadership Experience
- Typography
- Prototyping

Experience

Graphic Designer

Freelance • San Francisco, California

09/2021 - Present

- Designed and delivered production-ready digital content using HTML and CSS
- Spearheaded complete rebranding for clients including logo design, typography, website design, and packaging)
- · Developed comprehensive company style guide and UI toolkits from the ground up
- Advised clients in a plethora of areas including non-profits, small business, and biotech

Art Director

Montecito Sequoia Lodge • Kings Canyon National Park, California

05/2018 - 09/2021

- Taught art classes on Typography, Color Theory, and Fine Arts to camp clients ages
 1-90 yrs old
- Created weekly schedules based on a diverse range of art mediums, client requests, and availability of materials
- Enhanced client experiences through one on one instruction and addressing concerns

Art Teacher

Gnarly Studio · Los Altos, California

09/2020 - 12/2020

- Provided 2 hour weekly lessons to 4 clients with detailed lesson plans based on students' current knowledge and desire for increased artistic skills
- Managed & supplied private studio

Co-Founder

Cultured Stickers • San Francisco, California

08/2016 - 12/2018

- Small sticker company, #2 on Etsy
- Designed, produced & shipped stickers for an international clientele
- · Created custom orders upon request